sli.mg 2016-10-28

# sli.mg - 1.1 Privacy Policy

## Personal Data Protection

Sli.mg/ioimg.com does not disclose to any third party Private Data you have given us whatsoever. There are no affiliates or third parties who are given any access to data submitted to us. The only exception, obviously, is if we are forced to disclose the information as a result of a subpoena or other legal process. You may correct, amend, or delete inaccurate Private Data information you have given us. For legal and disaster recovery reasons we may retain backup and/or archival copies of information. We take every reasonable precaution to protect your Private Data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. 

You are responsible for taking every reasonable precaution on your end to protect any unauthorized person from accessing your Sli.mg/ioimg.com account. 

If you have any questions about our use of your Private Data, please contact us at admin@sli.mg 

We may revise our privacy policy from time to time by posting the changes here. 

Automatically collected technical information:   
At this time, we do not log information about each computer that access our site.   
However, we do log the IP Address of each computer that uploads Media / Albums. This information is stored in case there is a report of illegal Media stored on our servers. We will remove all Media associated to the IP Address and ban that IP Address from being able to upload in the future. 

We may use cookies, web beacons, or other anonymous tracking information to improve our server's interaction with your computer, and we may partner with third party advertisers who may (themselves or through their partners) place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. These cookies enable more customized ads, content or services to be provided to you. To trigger these cookies, we may pass an encrypted or "hashed" (non-human readable) identifier corresponding to your email address to a Web advertising partner, who may place a cookie on your computer. No personally identifiable information is on, or is connected to, these cookies. Although our servers currently don't respond to "do-not-track" requests, you can block these cookies in other ways, for example by going to <http://www.privacychoice.org/choose>. 

Personal data you choose to give us: We collect whatever personal data about you that you choose to give us, such as name, address, email address, profile information, and credit card billing information. We consider such personal data to be "Private Data," and subject to the "Personal Data Protection" paragraph above, with the following exception: Any data (text, images, videos, etc.) you post to a public forum on our site, linked to or from our site, or share via a social networking or promotional function, will not be considered "Private Data" and will not be subject to the "Personal Data Protection" paragraph above.
